<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>first on Wolfgangs Page</title>
    <link>https://wolfgangbach.github.io/tags/first/</link>
    <description>Recent content in first on Wolfgangs Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wolfgangbach.github.io/tags/first/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Johannesburg</title>
      <link>https://wolfgangbach.github.io/2023/10/05/the-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfgangbach.github.io/2023/10/05/the-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Johannesburg: A Memorable Adventure Stepping foot in Johannesburg after a grueling 20-hour journey, I knew I was in for an exciting and challenging experience. My first task was to secure a reliable internet connection at the airport, enabling me to book an Uber or Bolt ride to my hostel. Although it took more than an hour to get the Wi-Fi working, I finally succeeded. Little did I know that another hurdle awaited me just outside the secure area where families and friends typically gather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kruger</title>
      <link>https://wolfgangbach.github.io/2023/10/05/the-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfgangbach.github.io/2023/10/05/the-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the Wildlife in Kruger (30.05) Our journey began with Juan&amp;rsquo;s booking of an early morning driving tour with a knowledgeable guide for a mere $20. The irresistible deal prompted us to join him on this adventure. Riding in a classic safari jeep with seats in the back, we embarked on an exhilarating tour through Kruger National Park. The diverse wildlife we encountered left us in awe - graceful giraffes, majestic elephants, colorful birds, graceful antelopes, playful zebras, and even a few curious chickens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>https://wolfgangbach.github.io/2023/10/05/the-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolfgangbach.github.io/2023/10/05/the-first-post/</guid>
      <description>The first little post Welcome, dear reader! It&amp;rsquo;s great to have you here on my brand new webpage.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in learning more about me, please feel free to check out the About Me section.
I&amp;rsquo;m still new to building websites, so there maybe some issues here and there. This website was built using Hugo, which is a static webpage tool that heavily utilizes markdown.
That&amp;rsquo;s all for now, but if you need to contact me, the best way to reach me is through email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
